freemmorpglist.com 2015-02-09

# Privacy.

FREEMMORPGList.Com created by **Online Ocigrup S.L**

Dirección: Avenida Sarria, 52-54, 1º-2ª, 08029 Barcelona  
Telf.: +34 93 494 06 98  
Fax: +34 93 494 12 01  
CIF: B64948318  
info'@'ocigrup'.'com

Datos Legales: R.M. de Barcelona, Tomo 40813, Folio21, Hoja B375951, Inscripción1

Privacy Policy for FREEMMORPGList.Com

The privacy of our visitors to FREEMMORPGList.Com is important to us. 

At FREEMMORPGList.Com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit FREEMMORPGList.Com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on FREEMMORPGList.Com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by Jen Sense 

Protección de Datos: 

Data Protection Statement 

This data protection statement tells you about what personal data are collected by Online OciGrup SL, in the context of our Internet offerts and games and how those data are processed and used. Protecting your personal information is very important to us. Your data are assured against misuse and loss with numerous electronic, technical, physical, contractual and administrative measures. Online OciGrup has taken technical and organizational measures to ensure that both our internal and external collaborators take into account the instructions of the protection of data. 

Data Collection 

OciGrup Online collects personal data...

• That you enter when registering on our website or one of our games.  
• If you enter them in order to perform a query.  
• If you want to voluntarily participate in surveys or advertising campaigns, or receive newsletters.  
In connection with the use of our websites, forums and games, Online OciGrup collects the following personal data:  
• Cookies, Flash local data  
• Statistical information, for example, browser type, operating system, URL that directed you to our website, date, time, pages used, duration of use, frequency of use However, these are not used for any personal use, but only for statistical evaluation of anonymous data. 

Use of your data 

We use your personal data for ...

• the fulfilment and payment of our services.  
• anonymously and / or half anonymously, create and improve our offers so that they suit the needs.  
• meet legal obligations, particularly the duties of conservation.  
We also use your information to contact you. This includes, in particular, the preparation of grants and support, as well as the preparation of important information about your contract. Always with your consent, we inform you regularly about news, events and actions, for example, by email. 

Data transmission 

We treat your data in strictest confidence and, therefore, we will not pass them on to third parties. However, in rare cases we may be required by law to transfer data, for example, to the investigation offices. In these cases, the transmission will take place only in accordance with the legal bases. 

In isolated cases we employ subsidiary companies parent companies or third parties to fulfill certain services related to our work. This concerns especially to the payment process through external partners (Paypal, Global Collect, etc.) As well as in cases of delay via collection companies. These external companies are obligated to handle your data safely and confidentially and these can only be used to the extent that the performance of their duties is required. 

Right of revocation and data deletion 

If you have given us your consent for the processing of your personal data you may revoke it at any time. Online Ocigrup SL deletes your personal data as far as these are no longer needed or if you have requested it. Note that data can not be deleted when there are duties of conservation or even when we need them for the collection of our services. 

Information, data verification and elimination 

Through the email 'info`@'ocigrup´.com you may request consultation, modification or elimination of the data we have kept about you. Also, you can do it using our postal address: Online OciGrup S.L.  
Av. Sarria 52-54   
08029 Barcelona – Spain

If you have general questions about this data protection statement or about the data protection of OciGrup Online, we are available at the address info@ocigrup.com. In your queries, let us know if it is possible your User ID, email address and, when appropriate, the game you play. Barcelona 1 de Junio 2010  
Online OciGrup   
Av Sarria 52-54  
08029 Barcelona - Spain 

Tel.: +34 93 494 06 98  
Fax: +34 93 494 12 01
